<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>italki Design</title>
    <description>Designing great products</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 14:23:41 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 14:23:41 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.3</generator>

    
      <item>
        <title>Good Design Portfolio is Good Story</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;While in the progress of hiring more talents to form up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.figma.com/proto/0Oo3T11vTL8k63xTa82UfP/Team-Structure?node-id=0%3A49&amp;amp;viewport=165%2C533%2C0.08338088542222977&amp;amp;scaling=min-zoom&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;the new design structure&lt;/a&gt;, I have reviewed dozens of designer’s resumes and portfolios. I realized that most designers just put together all the works they’ve done before, try to make the portfolio as long as possible. And hope that it would sell themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It certainly doesn’t work that way. I feel it is necessary to write down some notes about what I think is a good design portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;make-it-visually-appealing&quot;&gt;Make it visually appealing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes I know I wrote the title as “Good Design Portfolio is Good Story”. However, the recruiter and hiring manager usually have busy calendars. If your portfolio looks boring, you already missed the opportunity to get their attentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Design is not only about making a nice picture, but don’t forget that making a nice picture is still a big part of design.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus there is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://lawsofux.com/aesthetic-usability-effect/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Aesthetics Usability Effect&lt;/a&gt;. A visually appealing portfolio definitely gives you higher chances to get to the next step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;craft-your-narrative&quot;&gt;Craft your narrative&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you’ve got the attention from the reader, it is all about telling a good story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your portfolio serves the purpose of telling the story of yourself. Make sure you craft your story with good narratives. Think about your portfolio as a product and the readers as users, think about how they would read your story and what might interest them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pay attention to the information architecture. Highlight the key points as necessary, so that your reader can quickly scan through the story before they decide to dive into the details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tell-me-who-you-are&quot;&gt;Tell me who you are&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After going through the portfolio, your reader should be able to have a good picture of who you are and what can you do. What’s better is that you can specify it by yourself and support it with all the sample works in your portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NP4lrVIpbvo&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;I’m Winston Wolf, I solve problems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;write-down-the-problem-the-process-then-the-solution&quot;&gt;Write down the problem, the process, then the solution&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When writing about your projects, always make sure to phrase the problems and/or the goals to achieve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tell the story about the process of how you approached to solve the problems. Sometimes also write down the mistakes you made along the way - don’t be surprised, the ability to summarize and reflect from the mistakes you made, is always a plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If applicable, also list out the results and impacts of your solution. Your reader is probably not going to dig into all the details and evaluate how good your solution is, but as the creator of the design solution, you should always be proud of what you delivered (otherwise why bothering putting it in your portfolio?). Highlight the parts that you are mostly proud of, share the passion with the readers even if they might not really care about it that much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;specify-your-role&quot;&gt;Specify your role&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take all the credits you deserved but don’t forget to mention your teammates. Often times we tend to highlight the projects that we worked on independently. It is true that these projects can highlight your professional skills. But in most cases it is as important for the hiring manager to understand how well you worked with your team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can highlight the moments when you showcased leadership, and be honest and clear with all the supports you got from your peers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;better-to-have-a-website&quot;&gt;Better to have a website&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sending PDFs is okay, but as a digital designer, it is always a plus to have a dedicated website hosting all your works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just to make sure that you have optimized and tested the loading speed. Prepare backup solutions if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;dont-zip-a-folder-with-all-the-works-you-have-done-before&quot;&gt;Don’t zip a folder with all the works you have done before&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is your job to highlight the best of yourself through the best of your works. Make it one single source of truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dont-send-dribbble-or-behance-links-only&quot;&gt;Don’t send Dribbble or Behance links only&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They could be good “read more” contents, but never use them as the portfolio itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dont-send-baiduyun-links&quot;&gt;Don’t send BaiduYun links&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because it sucks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dont-rar&quot;&gt;Don’t RAR&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is year 2021, use zip if you have to compress file size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;dont-reveal-confidential-contents&quot;&gt;Don’t reveal confidential contents&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is unprofessional.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021/02/19/good-design-portfolio-is-good-story/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021/02/19/good-design-portfolio-is-good-story/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From Sketch to Figma</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We switched our design tool from Sketch to Figma in August, 2019. Looking back, there are a few thoughts worth sharing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sketch&quot;&gt;Sketch&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sketch is by far the No.1 design tool in digital product design industry. I was one of the first group of people in the industry to try out Sketch. I started to use Sketch from version 2, and paid for the upgrade to version 3, paid again when they moved out of the Mac App Store, and then switched to their subscription model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/0.png&quot; alt=&quot;sketch&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was a big fan of Sketch since the beginning and I acted almost like an evangelist to convince my fellow designer friends to made the switch from Adobe to Sketch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;figma&quot;&gt;Figma&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I knew Figma since 2016, their CTO and co-founder wrote a blog post introducing the “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.figma.com/blog/introducing-vector-networks/&quot;&gt;Vector Networks&lt;/a&gt;”, explaining how advanced their algorithm was compared with other existing tools (like Sketch). I wasn’t really interested into it but still I decided to give it a try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/1.png&quot; alt=&quot;figma&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I was disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making an icon wasn’t super easy in Sketch, but it was quite ok - not really a pain point. The new approach of Figma might have some technical advantages but I didn’t even try to play with it. Because,  as a UI design tool, Figma’s UI by that time, was terrible!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a designer who has to look at the screen 10+ hours every day, I couldn’t  look at he pure black background and the pure white icons and text labels. I bet there were already lots of nice features there but it lost me on the first sight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Lesson learnt: People DO judge a book by its cover. Make your app prettier before rolling out PR articles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first impression wasn’t great, for the following years, Figma was actively posting news and blogs  in the design community. I gave it a few more tries later, and still, I was disappointed every time - by the same ugly interface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was at a very late stage until I realized, that the problem was in their sample file - which was using the pure black and white combination. Actually you can manually change the background yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Second lesson learnt: If your first impression wasn’t good enough, it is hard to win the date back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/2.png&quot; alt=&quot;figma sample&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, did I even mention that they used the pure red as the accent color (on top of black)?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-turn-over&quot;&gt;The turn over&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 3 months before I joined italki, I was working on a personal project with a remote developer partner. We used to use Sketch + Measure (a free plugin for handoff) + dropbox to sync our working files. I needed to renew my Sketch license by that time. Syncing data via dropbox wasn’t efficient enough, so I thought, maybe give Figma another try?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I tried to import my Sketch files into Figma, and realized that - wow, it doesn’t have to have a black background! I spent some time cleaning up the Sketch import, then started to share it with my partner - and I was blowed away!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real-time collaboration, the comments, the built-in handoff, the customized assets download, everything was sooooooo damn good for remote collaborators!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It did take some efforts to get used to Figma’s way of designing and organizing the artboards. I was also missing some handy functions and plugins which were only available in Sketch, but, THERE IS NO WAY BACK!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/3.png&quot; alt=&quot;goodbye&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Goodbye Sketch, we were in love for the past 7~8 years and we had a great time together, but sorry darling, it is time to say goodbye. There is nothing wrong about you, it is just that I’ve found my new soul mate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;made-the-switch-in-italki&quot;&gt;Made the switch in italki&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I joined italki, I had no intention to made the switch anytime soon. However, when I tried to understand how the team was organizing and sharing the design assets. I had a hard time to get the right assets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/4.png&quot; alt=&quot;folder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, there is nothing wrong with the folder structure, it was actually organized super well. But still, you have to download different files to check whether it is the one you were looking for. The lack of thumbnails and previews, and all the downloading/syncing made the process super slow and difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That made me start to think whether we should make the switch to Figma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;pros-and-cons&quot;&gt;Pros and Cons&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Switching to a new platform is never an easy decision. We need to evaluate the migration cost, the communication cost, the drawbacks during the transition, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Pros were clear:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Everything in the cloud, no more downloading and syncing. And no more Mac only limitation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Multiple designers can work on a same project simultaneously, with version control.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Developers can inspect the design directly in the cloud, no more exporting and/or uploading.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Everyone can have a free account for viewing, inspecting and commenting the design, no more shared Zeplin account.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Product managers and content writers can potentially work in the same environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Cons on the other hand were not super clear:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How much does it take for the team to learn the new tool?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How much does it cost to convert all the Sketch files into Figma?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sketch has a matured ecosystem with all the plugins and 3rd-party tools, while Figma was still pretty closed, if it doesn’t offer a certain function, there is no workaround.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;While migrating, would it slow down the overall product development process?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decision was made pretty quick, though. The team were able to get started with Figma basics pretty soon and we migrated a few key files into Figma - it wasn’t perfect and lots of manual tweaks had to be done. Our strategy was to use the import as a basic reference, and rebuild everything while designing new features. It worked pretty well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My supervisor, our co-founder and CPO, Yongyue Jiang, was also very supportive on this. He quickly setup the team account and paid the bills. We then quickly replaced the Sketch-to-Zeplin workflow with the all-in-one Figma solution. We did pay necessary communication cost along the way, but generally the transition was much smoother than expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-limitations&quot;&gt;The Limitations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We did met with a few issues during and after switching to Figma. One of the biggest concern was the lack of prototyping solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A big miss in the italki design team was that we didn’t make enough prototypes — As a matter of fact, we made zero prototypes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figma did support basic page-to-page transitions, and it actually worked much better than Sketch’s built-in prototype tool, but still it was too limited. With Sketch we can have 3rd-party solutions like Flinto and Principle, but with Figma we were stuck there with the basic tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things started to get promising when Figma released the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.figma.com/blog/announcing-smart-animate-and-advanced-transitions/&quot;&gt;Smart Animate&lt;/a&gt; feature, as well as an open plugin marketplace, which opened up a whole new world of possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Till now we are still looking for a better prototyping solution on Figma, but a lot of work could already have been done there. The bigger problem to solve is that, we are still NOT using them yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Come on team, let’s start to make your design alive!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People say that Figma is basically Sketch + inVision + Zeplin. I would say that it is much more than that. The collaboration capability had improved both our internal and external communications, the cloud-based solution allows it to be seamlessly integrated into other working platforms like Confluence and Jira. The growing plugin marketplace gives it infinite possibilities for the future. And yet we are only just using the basic design functions of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;is-figma-the-king-of-the-future&quot;&gt;Is Figma the King of the future?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve given too much praise to Figma. So does it mean it is the King of the future?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not necessarily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeing Sketch is chasing back after Figma now, by releasing the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sketch.com/for-teams/&quot;&gt;team plan&lt;/a&gt; as well as more cloud supports and live collaboration functions in the pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/5.png&quot; alt=&quot;sketch team&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, another promising tool, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.framer.com/&quot;&gt;FramerX&lt;/a&gt; is also raising up very quickly and taking up the market share. (By the way, it is much prettier than Figma!). The design tools and platforms are still in the middle of evolving and they are evolving really fast. Picking a right tool would help us get the job done in the right and faster way. Always keep an eye on what’s happening and never miss the chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/6.png&quot; alt=&quot;framer&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an ending note, keep an eye on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.framer.com/web/](https://www.framer.com/web/)&quot;&gt;web version of Framer&lt;/a&gt; and see how it performs when it comes public, this might be our next move.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/08/sketch2figma/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020/03/08/sketch2figma/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mike Monteiro: 13 Ways Designers Screw Up Client Presentations</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A good designer who can sell work is more valuable than a great designer who can’t. &lt;br /&gt;
The hardest part of design is presenting work. I’ve seen people who did amazing work get up in front of a client and lay eggs. I’ve also seen people do alright work and wind clients around their little finger. Optimally, you want to do good work and present it well. But I’d rather have a good designer who can present well than a great designer who can’t. Work that can’t be sold is as useless as the designer who can’t sell it. Presenting is a core design skill. In this session we’ll go over the most common mistakes designers make when presenting their work, and how to avoid them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/121082134&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-seeing-the-client-as-someone-they-have-to-please&quot;&gt;1. Seeing the client as someone they have to please&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;happiness is a side-effect of good design, not a goal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-not-getting-off-your-ass&quot;&gt;2. Not getting off your ass&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-starting-with-an-apology&quot;&gt;3. Starting with an apology&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-not-setting-the-stage-properly&quot;&gt;4. Not setting the stage properly&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-giving-the-real-estate-tour&quot;&gt;5. Giving the real estate tour&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;6-taking-notes&quot;&gt;6. Taking notes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;7-reading-a-script&quot;&gt;7. Reading a script&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;8-getting-defensive&quot;&gt;8. Getting defensive&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;9-mentioning-typefaces&quot;&gt;9. Mentioning typefaces&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;10-talking-about-how-hard-you-worked&quot;&gt;10. Talking about how hard you worked&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;11-reacting-to-questions-as-change-requests&quot;&gt;11. Reacting to questions as change requests&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;12-not-guiding-the-feedback-loop&quot;&gt;12. Not guiding the feedback loop&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;13-asking-do-you-like-it&quot;&gt;13. Asking “Do you like it?”&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;and-one-weird-trick-that-you-wont-believe-works-every-time&quot;&gt;…and one weird trick that you won’t believe works every time.&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn the client’s goddamn name.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/06/13-ways-designers-screw-up-client-presentations/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020/03/06/13-ways-designers-screw-up-client-presentations/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>译文：成绩不佳的产品设计师的7个迹象</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-signs-of-an-underachieving-product-designer&quot;&gt;7 signs of an underachieving product designer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;原文：&lt;a href=&quot;https://uxdesign.cc/7-signs-of-an-underperforming-product-designer-df4a49029299&quot;&gt;https://uxdesign.cc/7-signs-of-an-underperforming-product-designer-df4a49029299&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1他们从不问为什么they-never-ask-why&quot;&gt;1.他们从不问为什么/They never ask why&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;产品设计师最终是体验的管理者。如果他（她）没有像幼儿那样质疑，那是一个不好的信号。不问问题会导致功能膨胀。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;2他们有过多的注释和文档they-have-excessive-amounts-of-notes-and-documentation&quot;&gt;2.他们有过多的注释和文档/They have excessive amounts of notes and documentation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;记录思想和数据是保持组织结构和获取关键信息以进行设计决策的重要组成部分。但是，如果数据如此密集且过于复杂，以致于您无法检索重要信息或识别模式，那么它必然会陷入瘫痪。什么都没做。
如果产品设计师无法简明扼要地记录或实时进行合成，那么这是一个不好的信号，表明他或她将无法利用经过多小时，几天或几周的研究而收集到的数据。收集它。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;3他们不做原型they-dont-prototype&quot;&gt;3.他们不做原型/They don’t prototype&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;如果一张图片价值1000字，那么一个原型价值1000次会议。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;4他们对旅行没有兴趣they-have-no-interest-in-traveling&quot;&gt;4.他们对旅行没有兴趣/They have no interest in traveling&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;研究表明，个人的创造力水平（以及促进创造力的开放态度）可以直接受到其旅行次数的影响。更重要的是，旅行使设计师能够更深入地了解文化，语言和经验。
迪特勒·拉姆斯（Dieter Rams）曾经说过：“如果不了解别人，就不会理解好的设计。” 将自己沉浸在不同的文化中，将启发微妙的细微差别，这些细微差别塑造了我们的思维方式和我们所处的环境。如果产品设计师至少不希望出国旅行，那么他或她同情用户的能力可能会受到限制。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;5他们没有在纸上画草稿they-dont-sketch-their-ideas&quot;&gt;5.他们没有在纸上画草稿/They don’t sketch their ideas&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;即使是最优秀，最有经验的设计师也是错误的，而且大多数时候他们都是错误的。这就是设计在协作和迭代时更成功的原因。能够尽快完成所有想法既是增加创造力的一种手段，也是您和更重要的用户的反馈速度的一种手段。
如果设计师开始使用一种设计工具，而不是使用笔和纸，那么他或她的移动速度就不够快，浪费了从不可避免的错误中学习的时间。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;6他们不使用最新的设计工具they-dont-use-the-latest-design-tools&quot;&gt;6.他们不使用最新的设计工具/They don’t use the latest design tools&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;我知道这似乎很琐碎。&lt;/strong&gt;但是现实是，自满会杀死人。如果产品设计师不了解该行业使用的最新工具，则可能表明他/她没有积极寻求提高效率的方法。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;7他们责怪开发they-blame-developers&quot;&gt;7.他们责怪开发/They blame developers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;如果设计的最终实现与预期不符（请阅读：pixel-perfect），那是设计者的错。他或她或者不了解什么在技术上可行，或者在编写代码时没有与开发人员有效地沟通以进行课程纠正。应该期望设计师创造愉悦的体验，其中包括与队友互动的经历。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/01/7-signs-of-an-underachieving-product-designer/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020/03/01/7-signs-of-an-underachieving-product-designer/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>译文：A complete guide to iconography</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;原文地址：&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.designsystems.com/iconography-guide/&quot;&gt;https://www.designsystems.com/iconography-guide/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‍&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;图标是任何设计系统或产品体验的关键部分。图标可帮助我们快速导航。它们与语言无关。最好的是：它们实际上很小，因此它们不会占用太多房地产。图标是良好设计系统的基本组成部分，对于营销材料非常有帮助。它们是插图内容的基础构建块，但是它们也是高度技术性的。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;喜欢设计图标的人并不多，而擅长设计图标的人就更少了。我写了本指南来帮助您成为其中的一员。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‍&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/1.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;无论您是设计系统专家，插图画家还是产品设计师，本指南都将帮助您学习如何构建图标，如何使它们与您的品牌保持一致以及如何将其实现到设计系统中。让我们从基础开始。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;图标的基本元素&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;图标的基本元素&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;尺寸&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;尺寸&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;一致性是使用图标的关键，并且在构建图标时，所有图标的大小都应相同。首先，您需要确保知道如何构建网格（8或10的倍数？）。从那里开始，您的基本图标大小应与此直接相关。因此，如果您有一个基于8s的网格，则希望以16、24或32进行构建。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;选择一个通用尺寸来构建所有图标，然后让您的工程师缩放到其他设计师可能需要的其他尺寸。您不想一遍又一遍地构建相同的图标。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;当您需要字形复杂性时，那就是您要开始添加大小的时候。您可能将基本产品图标的像素设置为24px，但由于使用上的巨大差异，营销图标的像素设置为80px。您需要为那些较大的尺寸添加细节。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/2.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;24x24、40x40和80x80的商店图标&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;当以不同尺寸构建相同的图标时，我喜欢从最大尺寸开始，然后向下滚动。我发现删除细节和简化要容易得多，而不是在上手时添加。在真正最小化对象之前，还可以使您感觉到对象。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;颜色&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;颜色&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;对于产品图标，请使用1种颜色：黑色。除此之外，您的组件也将变得过于复杂和难以为其他设计师所利用。对于营销图标，如果它是品牌的重要组成部分，则可能要使用两种颜色，但是我个人认为图标应该是一种颜色。具有3种或更多颜色的任何东西都是插图，而不是图标。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/3.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;
左：这是一个现场插图。中：带有透视图的图标。右：平面图标。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;网格&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;网格&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;该&lt;strong&gt;像素网格&lt;/strong&gt;是使用最小增量的根本格：一个像素。构建图标时，您始终希望将对象与像素网格对齐，尤其是直线。但是，您可以在像素网格上构建其他形状（如果您使用的是Figma，那么您已经是自动的）。您想要在像素网格上构建对象，不仅是因为它可以更好地渲染，还因为它使您的生活更轻松。当使用网格时，均匀地排列东西要容易得多。它可以帮助您与位置保持一致，并且总体上可以使您的图标看起来更好。您可以在Figma中轻松看到“像素上”与“关闭”之间的区别。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/4.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;左：在像素上。右：关闭像素。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;在开始之前，我喜欢为自己构建一个网格。这是我在Figma中的设置。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/5.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;大！现在，您已经掌握了像素网格，您将要了解光学网格。光栅可以帮助我们确定图标的质心在哪里，以及人眼感知到的大小。圆形和弯曲的物体比正方形占用更少的视觉空间。最好将图标放在固定大小的容器中，以使它们在导出时都具有相同的尺寸。添加此固有填充可支持光学/感知加权，而无需在以后的开发中额外费神。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;在构建我的光栅时，我希望在等于笔触粗细的边缘进行填充，如果使用的是1px笔触，则可能加倍。您可以在下面的示例中看到不同的形状如何到达网格的不同边缘。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/6.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;在视觉上，主要对象应在垂直和水平方向上居中。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/7.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;优势对象（矩形）居中&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;如果您使用像素网格并利用光学网格，那么您将走在前面。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;描边和填充&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;描边和填充&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;还记得我说一致性是关键吗？我再说一遍。除了看到两个图标并排填充一个图标而另一个被抚摸时，没有什么比这更让我感到困扰。确保所有图标的样式都相同非常重要。例如，您可能有一些使用填充来显示某些内容的用例，但是您肯定要创建一种样式的集合，并可能创建另一种样式。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;通常，填充的图标具有较高的可识别性。描边的图标使您能够创建微小的细节。在选择哪种样式更合适时，您还应该考虑自己的整体品牌。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;如果要创建描边图标，则描边的权重必须相同。我还建议笔划之间的间距不要比您的笔划粗细。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/8.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;笔划之间的距离应尽可能反映出笔划重量&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;也许您有一个图标集可以满足一种样式，但不能满足另一种样式。创建描边图标的填充版本时，您将需要研究如何简化线条工作。理想情况下，填充图标就像阴影一样，而不是基于倒线的图标。创建填充图标的描边版本涉及确定可以容纳在空间中的描边粗细以及可以在保持清晰度的同时添加哪些细节。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/9.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;我不建议使描边的图标小于10px（假设描边粗细为1px-2px）。他们将很难破译。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;款式选择&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;款式选择&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;您的图标代表您的品牌。开始这项工作时，重要的是要了解品牌的核心价值及其在视觉上的体现。要考虑的一些形容词是硬/软，随意/正式，豪华/经济和字面/抽象的。您可能具有可以参考的插图样式。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;有些图标看起来很简单（X，汉堡菜单，人字形），但是这些图标要求您已经弄清楚了图标系统的基本原理。我建议从较难的图标（即更复杂的图标）开始，以帮助您确定要灌输哪些规则。这样，一旦您开始设计更简单的图标，便会变得轻而易举。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/10.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5种样式的5种产品图标-请注意，细微的差别会使每组感觉一致且整体。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;以下是反映公司视觉品牌的声音和色调的产品和营销图标的选择：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://brand.uber.com/guide#iconography-system-icons&quot;&gt;Uber&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://material.io/tools/icons/?style=baseline&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/design/human-interface-guidelines/ios/icons-and-images/system-icons/&quot;&gt;Apple&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zachroszczewski.com/airbnb/&quot;&gt;Airbnb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bonniekatewolf.com/icon-system.html/&quot;&gt;Square&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;绘图图标&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;绘图图标&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;几何形状&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;几何形状&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;除非创建非常自然的有机图标样式，否则我喜欢从基本形状开始创建图标的形式。矩形，正方形和圆形都为您提供了一个很好的起点，以创建更精美的图标。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/11.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;这只橡皮鸭是由圆形（和一个圆角矩形）制成的。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;绘制几何形式时，如果需要制作复杂的多边形，则可以从正方形或矩形开始，也可以使用钢笔工具从点到像素。这样做时，拥有清晰的网格尤为重要，这样您就可以看到这些点的去向。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;当您需要绘制&lt;strong&gt;成角度的几何形状时&lt;/strong&gt;，我不建议仅使用矩形并旋转它。而是使用像素网格绘制有角度的矩形。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/12.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;左：旋转的矩形（锚不与网格对齐）。右：手绘矩形（确保您的点与网格对齐）。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;自然形态&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;自然形态&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;在Figma中绘制更自然的形式很容易。您可以使用传统的逐点绘制曲线的方法，也可以使用Figma出色的点角半径工具。我喜欢将所有点绘制为直线，然后使用拐角半径工具将拐角圆化。该工具对于创建有机的，平衡的形状非常有用。由于Figma的角会自动调整，因此您可以在这些点附近移动，并且角会为您调整。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/13.gif&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;角球接球&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;角球/接球&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;拐角有两种选择：斜切（正方形），斜角和倒圆角。我强烈建议您坚持使用一种样式的图标集。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;转角半径&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;转角半径&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;将其用于圆角正方形和矩形时，要确保所有角的半径相同。创建同心形状时，需要调整角半径以创建完美的同心形状。内部形状的半径将小于外部形状。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/14.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;此公文包中的同心半径的大量示例&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;路径上的任何中间点都可以通过检查器中的“转角半径”属性进行舍入。如果选择整个路径，则会将所有角均以相同的角度倒圆。如果进入“编辑”模式，则可以选择单个点并将它们分别取整。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;端盖&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;端盖&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;端盖可以是圆形或方形的。坚持一个选择。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;填充对象&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;填充对象&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;当您的图标需要在其主要表单（例如房屋中的窗户）内部填充对象时，理想情况下，您希望将描边形状保留在描边图标中。并在填充的图标中填充对象。如果没有足够的空间容纳笔触形状，则需要使用与笔触成比例的填充形状。例如，如果笔划粗细为2px，则不希望填充的形状大于4x4px。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;隐喻&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;隐喻&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;隐喻在图标中很重要-我们一直在不加思索地使用它们。房子的图标表示主页。昆虫意味着错误。在缩放图标以创建较小版本时，我喜欢记住我在传达图标消息时所使用的隐喻。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/15.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;使用常见的隐喻以较小的尺寸继续，而不是简单地以较小的比例制作确切的图标。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/16.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;如果所有内容都不适合，请确定最重要的细节，然后删除多余的细节。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/17.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;如果受空间限制，您可以简化关键细节而不是删除它们。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;透视&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;透视&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;在图标中使用透视图是棘手的-由于使用透视图进行绘制会占用额外的空间，因此它们的大小变得很困难。如果您确实想使用透视图，则可以广泛地使用它并使之成为系统的关键部分，或者在有助于提高可读性和清晰度时谨慎使用。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/18.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;第一排：平坦。下排：透视图。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;文字避免&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;文字（避免！）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;尽可能避免用文字来带代表图标。图标是全球性的。如果确实需要类型（例如，货币符号），请自己绘制，而不要使用字体。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;工具提示&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;工具提示&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;布尔运算&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;布尔运算&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;布尔运算通过以下四个公式之一组合任意一组形状图层：并集，相减，相交和排除。这个工具是实时的，而且很棒。这是使图标更可编辑的好方法。您不必使用剪切路径，而可以使用并集功能。不想手动找到形状的交集？尝试减去。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/19.gif&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;布尔组被视为单个形状层并共享填充和笔触属性，并且可以通过后续的布尔操作与其他布尔组组合。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;联合&lt;/strong&gt;：联合将选定的形状组合为一个布尔组。如果对象重叠，则新形状的外部路径将包括其子层路径的组合减去任何重叠的线段。然后将笔划应用于该外部路径，而忽略彼此重叠的任何路径段。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;减法&lt;/strong&gt;：减法是Union的对立面。减法从基本形状中除去一个形状或一组形状的区域。只有底部形状层是实体，其余部分从中减去。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;相交&lt;/strong&gt;：相交会创建一个布尔组，其形状仅由其子层的重叠部分组成。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;排除&lt;/strong&gt;：排除与相交相反。排除仅显示其子层不重叠的区域。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;完成图标操作后，我想创建一个并集（如果这还不是一条大路），以便将来的设计师调整颜色时，只需更改一个属性（填充）即可填充和中风。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;矢量网络&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;矢量网络&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;向量网络是Figma中最独特的功能之一。大多数钢笔工具都按照定义的方向在回路中绘制路径，总是希望重新连接到其原始点。矢量网络没有方向，可以向不同的方向分叉，而无需创建单独的路径对象。与使用传统矢量路径工具绘制复杂对象相比，可以在同一对象内创建具有相同属性的复杂对象的速度要快得多。有关更多信息，请访问&lt;a href=&quot;https://help.figma.com/article/63-vector-networks/&quot;&gt;本文&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;如何在设计系统中使用图标&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;如何在设计系统中使用图标&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;使图标集可供团队其他成员访问是组织，资产管理和意识的问题。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;组织&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;组织&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;让我们从文件命名开始。您的图标应基于其显示的名称而不是其代表的名称。例如，秒表图标应命名为&lt;strong&gt;秒表&lt;/strong&gt;，而不是&lt;strong&gt;speed&lt;/strong&gt;。灯泡应该叫做&lt;strong&gt;灯泡&lt;/strong&gt;，而不是&lt;strong&gt;想法&lt;/strong&gt;。您想立即让人们知道图标是什么，而不是在概念上传达什么。名字越短越好。当您需要多个单词时，请使用破折号将它们分开。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/icon/20.png&quot; alt=&quot;immg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;像这样的图标可能需要多个单词，例如，chef-hat。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;最终，您将所有图标变成组件。在Figma中，组件的工作原理就像框架一样，其扭曲之处在于组件的副本会创建新的实例，而不是副本。这意味着您可以拥有一个包含所有图标的巨型库，并且在需要使用一个图标时，可以从该库中创建一个实例。如果有人更改了原件，则您的图标仍将是最新的。您可以搜索这些资产，因此您可能想要添加可搜索的信息。但是除了将其放在文件名中之外，还有一种选择。Figma有一个组件描述框，可让您添加标签和关键字。在这里添加人们在您的图书馆中可能正在搜索的所有短语而又无需做出疯狂的冗长而复杂的名字的好地方。这就是这些产品价值所在！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;为了帮助您的工程师，您需要同时使用框架和页面。页面代表最外面的分组（所以我喜欢按大小对它们进行排序）。然后，框架将帮助您缩小内容范围，如下例所示。该图标的命名系统为&lt;strong&gt;size&amp;gt; category&amp;gt; file name&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/5e59ee792c0cd9c7fe6a802d/5e5a05392089e51c9f84be6b_23-Organization.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/5e59ee792c0cd9c7fe6a802d/5e5a05392089e51c9f84be6b_23-Organization.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;当您使用带有变体的相同图标时，这就是我喜欢如何使用它们的方式。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;不同大小&lt;/strong&gt;：使用不同页面，因为您很少会直接从一个实例切换到另一个实例。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;填充与描边&lt;/strong&gt;：如果您同时使用两种样式，请在图标名称后使用斜杠表示填充或描边图标。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/5e59ee792c0cd9c7fe6a802d/5e5a05393fb2cce8996c89a5_24-Coffees.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/5e59ee792c0cd9c7fe6a802d/5e5a05393fb2cce8996c89a5_24-Coffees.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;左：咖啡/抚摸。右：咖啡/夹心&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;调整后的图像&lt;/strong&gt;：当您的图标带有视觉变体（例如，多种货币变体）时，也可以使用命名来帮助区分，使用的方法与填充图标和描边图标相同。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/5e59ee792c0cd9c7fe6a802d/5e5a0539c9fe84c9648ba651_25-Shields.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://uploads-ssl.webflow.com/5e59ee792c0cd9c7fe6a802d/5e5a0539c9fe84c9648ba651_25-Shields.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;左侧的原始图标为“盾牌”。然后，从左到右依次是“盾/美元”，“盾/欧元”，“盾/磅”，“盾/日元”，“盾/加”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;管理资产&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;管理资产&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;完成图标操作后，您希望它们尽可能干净以实现最佳导出效果。使用布尔运算简化您的工作（还记得我们的朋友Union吗？）。避免任何多余的线条或形状。检查所有线条是否都在框架内。绝对值得让另一个人查看您的所有图标并仔细检查是否整洁。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figma很棒，因为它鼓励协作和透明性。对于图标，允许所有设计人员都具有编辑权限，以便他们可以添加新图标，这很诱人。我建议单独收集图标，进行审核，并在达到标准时自行添加。给您的同事查看访问权限（以及对您的库的访问权限）足以使他们参与您所做的工作，而不必最终得到cattywampus库和文件。您的某些同事可能想要创建同一图标的不同版本（例如，以不同的颜色或名称）。当有人将图标与概念或产品相关联时，通常会发生这种情况。您永远不希望库中每个图标的版本超过一个。对于这些名称，请使用组件说明。您的同行设计师应该在各自的文件中而不是在母版中调整图标颜色。相信我，您将不得不不时对这些图标进行更改，并且您不想在一个以上的地方进行更改。当您准备导出图标时，文件格式是关键。如果您要向设计或工程团队以外的合作伙伴提供图标，则可能是给他们提供了.png文件。以1x，2x和3x导出以适合多种设备。对于工程和设计，通常会导出.svg文件，这些文件可以在设计程序中编辑，并在应用程序或网站上在线呈现时通过代码在浏览器中绘制。导出SVG时，您需要尽可能干净的代码。选择Figma的另一个重要原因是超最小的SVG导出。由于它们经过优化，它消除了进一步优化的需要。看看这个&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.figma.com/blog/with-figmas-new-svg-exports-less-more/&quot;&gt;文章&lt;/a&gt;以了解更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;将您的图标移交给他人&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;将您的图标移交给他人&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;您可以成为世界上最伟大的图标设计者，但是如果您无法在应用程序/网页/直接邮件中实现图标，那么它就没有任何用处。在开始设计之前，请与负责将这些产品投入产品的工程团队联系。他们将为您提供有关网站或应用程序基础结构的信息，这些信息将推动您的一些选择，例如笔触粗细或大小。询问其他设计师过去做过什么，以确保您不重复工作。从PMM中找出他们渴望看到的其他图标。成为一个友好的同事，要求人们提供反馈，建议和帮助。它将使您对应该做的事情有更好的了解，这样您就不会重做工作，也不会忽略其他人已经发现的关键租户。当你&lt;a href=&quot;https://johanronsse.be/2018/09/23/the-figma-api-for-the-rest-of-us/&quot;&gt;使用Figma的API以编程方式导出&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‍&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‍&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‍&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‍&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020/02/28/a-complete-guide-to-iconography/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020/02/28/a-complete-guide-to-iconography/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
