<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>italki Design</title>
    <description>Designing great products</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 22:49:00 +0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 22:49:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.3</generator>

    
      <item>
        <title>From Sketch to Figma</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We switched our design tool from Sketch to Figma in August, 2019. Looking back, there are a few thoughts that are worth sharing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sketch&quot;&gt;Sketch&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sketch is by far the No.1 design tool in digital product design industry. I was one of the first group of people in the industry to try out Sketch. I started to use Sketch from version 2, and paid for the upgrade to version 3, paid again when they moved out of the Mac App Store, and then switched to their subscription model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/0.png&quot; alt=&quot;sketch&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was a big fan of Sketch since the beginning and I acted almost like an evangelist to convince my fellow designer friends to made the switch from Adobe to Sketch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;figma&quot;&gt;Figma&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I knew Figma since 2016, their CTO and co-founder wrote a blog post introducing the “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.figma.com/blog/introducing-vector-networks/&quot;&gt;Vector Networks&lt;/a&gt;”, explaining how advanced their algorithm was compared with other existing tools (like Sketch). I wasn’t really interested into it but still I decided to give it a try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/1.png&quot; alt=&quot;figma&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I was disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making an icon wasn’t super easy in Sketch, but it was quite ok - not really a pain point. The new approach of Figma might have some technical advantages but I didn’t even try to play with it. Because,  as a UI design tool, Figma’s UI by that time, was terrible!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a designer how has to look at the screen 10+ hours every day, I couldn’t  look at he pure black background and the pure white icons and text labels. I bet there were already lots of nice features there but it lost me on the first sight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Lesson learnt: People DO judge a book by its cover. Make your app prettier before rolling out PR articles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first impression wasn’t great, for the following years, Figma was actively posting news and blogs  in the design community. I gave it a few more tries later, and still, I was disappointed every time - by the same ugly interface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was at a very late stage until I realized, that the problem was in their sample file - which was using the pure black and white combination. Actually you can manually change the background yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/2.png&quot; alt=&quot;figma sample&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, did I even mention that they used the pure red as the accent color (on top of black)?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Second lesson learnt: If your first impression wasn’t good enough, it is hard to win the date back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-turn-over&quot;&gt;The turn over&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About 3 months before I joined italki, I was working on a personal project with a remote developer partner. We used to use Sketch + Measure (a free plugin for handoff) + dropbox to sync our working files. I needed to renew my Sketch license by that time. Syncing data via dropbox wasn’t efficient enough, so I thought, maybe give Figma another try?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I tried to import my Sketch files into Figma, and realized that - wow, it doesn’t have to have a black background! I spent some time cleaning up the Sketch import, then started to share it with my partner - and I was blowed away!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real-time collaboration, the comments, the built-in handoff, the customized assets download, everything was sooooooo damn good for remote collaborators!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It did take some efforts to get used to Figma’s way of designing and organizing the artboards. I was also missing some handy functions and plugins which were only available in Sketch, but, THERE IS NO WAY BACK!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/3.png&quot; alt=&quot;goodbye&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Goodbye Sketch, we were in love for the past 7~8 years and we had a great time together, but sorry darling, it is time to say goodbye. There is nothing wrong about you, it is just that I’ve found my new soul mate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;made-the-switch-in-italki&quot;&gt;Made the switch in italki&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I joined italki, I had no intention to made the switch anytime soon. However, when I tried to understand how the team was organizing and sharing the design assets. I had a hard time to get the right assets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/4.png&quot; alt=&quot;folder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, there is nothing wrong with the folder structure, it was actually organized super well. But still, you have to download different files to check whether it is the one you were looking for. The lack of thumbnails and previews, and all the downloading/syncing made the process super slow and difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That made me start to think whether we should make the switch to Figma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;pros-and-cons&quot;&gt;Pros and Cons&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Switching to a new platform is never an easy decision. We need to evaluate the migration cost, the communication cost, the drawbacks during the transition, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Pros were clear:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Everything in the cloud, no more downloading and syncing. And no more Mac only limitation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Multiple designer can work on a same project simultaneously, with version control.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Developers can inspect the design directly in the cloud, no more exporting and/or uploading.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Everyone can have a free account for viewing, inspecting and commenting the design, no more shared Zeplin account.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Product managers and content writers can potentially work in the same environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Cons on the other hand were not super clear:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How much does it take for the team to learn the new tool?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How much does it cost to convert all the Sketch files into Figma?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sketch has a matured ecosystem with all the plugins and 3rd-party tools, while Figma was still pretty closed, if it doesn’t offer a certain function, there is no workaround.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;While migrating, would it slow down the overall product development process?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decision was made pretty quick, though. The team were able to get started with Figma basics pretty soon and we migrated a few key files into Figma - it wasn’t perfect and lots of manual tweaks had to be done. Our strategy was to use the import as a basic reference, and rebuild everything while designing new features. It worked pretty well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;mbnb&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My supervisor, our co-founder and CPO, Yongyue Jiang, was also very supportive on this. He quickly setup the team account and paid the bills. We then quickly replaced the Sketch-to-Zeplin workflow with the all-in-one Figma solution. We did pay necessary communication cost along the way, but generally the transition was much smoother than expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-limitations&quot;&gt;The Limitations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We did met with a few issues during and after switching to Figma. One of the biggest concern was the lack of prototyping solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One big miss in the italki design team was that we didn’t make enough prototypes — As a matter of fact, we made zero prototypes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Figma did support basic page-to-page transitions, and it actually worked much better than Sketch’s built-in prototype tool, but still it was too limited. With Sketch we can have 3rd-party solutions like Flinto and Principle, but with Figma we are stuck there with the basic tools.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things started to get promising when Figma released the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.figma.com/blog/announcing-smart-animate-and-advanced-transitions/&quot;&gt;Smart Animate&lt;/a&gt; feature, as well as an open plugin marketplace, which opened up a whole new world of possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Till now we are still looking for a better prototyping solution on Figma, but a lot of work could already have been done there. The bigger problem to solve is that, we are still NOT using them yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Come on team, let’s start to make your design alive!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People say that Figma is basically Sketch + inVision + Zeplin. I would say that it is much more than that. The collaboration capability had improved both our internal and external communications, the cloud-based solution allows it to be seamlessly integrated into other working platforms like Confluence and Jira. The growing plugin marketplace gives it infinite possibilities for the future. And yet we are only just using the basic design functions of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;is-figma-the-king-of-the-future&quot;&gt;Is Figma the King of the future&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve given too much praise to Figma. So does it mean it is the King of the future?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not necessarily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are seeing Sketch is chasing back after Figma now, by releasing the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sketch.com/for-teams/&quot;&gt;team plan&lt;/a&gt; as well as more cloud supports and live collaboration functions in the pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/5.png&quot; alt=&quot;sketch team&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, another promising tool, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.framer.com/&quot;&gt;FramerX&lt;/a&gt; is also raising up very quickly and taking up the market share. (By the way, it is much prettier than Figma!). The design tools and platforms are still in the middle of evolving and they are evolving really fast. Picking a right tool would help us get the job done in the right and faster way. Always keep an eye on what’s happening and never miss the chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/posts/sketch2figma/6.png&quot; alt=&quot;framer&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an ending note, keep an eye on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.framer.com/web/](https://www.framer.com/web/)&quot;&gt;web version of Framer&lt;/a&gt; and see how it performs when it comes public, this might be our next move.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/08/sketch2figma/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020/03/08/sketch2figma/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mike Monteiro: 13 Ways Designers Screw Up Client Presentations</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A good designer who can sell work is more valuable than a great designer who can’t. &lt;br /&gt;
The hardest part of design is presenting work. I’ve seen people who did amazing work get up in front of a client and lay eggs. I’ve also seen people do alright work and wind clients around their little finger. Optimally, you want to do good work and present it well. But I’d rather have a good designer who can present well than a great designer who can’t. Work that can’t be sold is as useless as the designer who can’t sell it. Presenting is a core design skill. In this session we’ll go over the most common mistakes designers make when presenting their work, and how to avoid them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/121082134&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-seeing-the-client-as-someone-they-have-to-please&quot;&gt;1. Seeing the client as someone they have to please&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;happiness is a side-effect of good design, not a goal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-not-getting-off-your-ass&quot;&gt;2. Not getting off your ass&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-starting-with-an-apology&quot;&gt;3. Starting with an apology&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-not-setting-the-stage-properly&quot;&gt;4. Not setting the stage properly&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-giving-the-real-estate-tour&quot;&gt;5. Giving the real estate tour&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;6-taking-notes&quot;&gt;6. Taking notes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;7-reading-a-script&quot;&gt;7. Reading a script&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;8-getting-defensive&quot;&gt;8. Getting defensive&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;9-mentioning-typefaces&quot;&gt;9. Mentioning typefaces&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;10-talking-about-how-hard-you-worked&quot;&gt;10. Talking about how hard you worked&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;11-reacting-to-questions-as-change-requests&quot;&gt;11. Reacting to questions as change requests&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;12-not-guiding-the-feedback-loop&quot;&gt;12. Not guiding the feedback loop&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;13-asking-do-you-like-it&quot;&gt;13. Asking “Do you like it?”&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;and-one-weird-trick-that-you-wont-believe-works-every-time&quot;&gt;…and one weird trick that you won’t believe works every time.&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn the client’s goddamn name.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/06/13-ways-designers-screw-up-client-presentations/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020/03/06/13-ways-designers-screw-up-client-presentations/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>译文：成绩不佳的产品设计师的7个迹象</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-signs-of-an-underachieving-product-designer&quot;&gt;7 signs of an underachieving product designer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;原文：&lt;a href=&quot;https://uxdesign.cc/7-signs-of-an-underperforming-product-designer-df4a49029299&quot;&gt;https://uxdesign.cc/7-signs-of-an-underperforming-product-designer-df4a49029299&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1他们从不问为什么they-never-ask-why&quot;&gt;1.他们从不问为什么/They never ask why&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;产品设计师最终是体验的管理者。如果他（她）没有像幼儿那样质疑，那是一个不好的信号。不问问题会导致功能膨胀。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;2他们有过多的注释和文档they-have-excessive-amounts-of-notes-and-documentation&quot;&gt;2.他们有过多的注释和文档/They have excessive amounts of notes and documentation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;记录思想和数据是保持组织结构和获取关键信息以进行设计决策的重要组成部分。但是，如果数据如此密集且过于复杂，以致于您无法检索重要信息或识别模式，那么它必然会陷入瘫痪。什么都没做。
如果产品设计师无法简明扼要地记录或实时进行合成，那么这是一个不好的信号，表明他或她将无法利用经过多小时，几天或几周的研究而收集到的数据。收集它。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;3他们不做原型they-dont-prototype&quot;&gt;3.他们不做原型/They don’t prototype&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;如果一张图片价值1000字，那么一个原型价值1000次会议。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;4他们对旅行没有兴趣they-have-no-interest-in-traveling&quot;&gt;4.他们对旅行没有兴趣/They have no interest in traveling&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;研究表明，个人的创造力水平（以及促进创造力的开放态度）可以直接受到其旅行次数的影响。更重要的是，旅行使设计师能够更深入地了解文化，语言和经验。
迪特勒·拉姆斯（Dieter Rams）曾经说过：“如果不了解别人，就不会理解好的设计。” 将自己沉浸在不同的文化中，将启发微妙的细微差别，这些细微差别塑造了我们的思维方式和我们所处的环境。如果产品设计师至少不希望出国旅行，那么他或她同情用户的能力可能会受到限制。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;5他们没有在纸上画草稿they-dont-sketch-their-ideas&quot;&gt;5.他们没有在纸上画草稿/They don’t sketch their ideas&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;即使是最优秀，最有经验的设计师也是错误的，而且大多数时候他们都是错误的。这就是设计在协作和迭代时更成功的原因。能够尽快完成所有想法既是增加创造力的一种手段，也是您和更重要的用户的反馈速度的一种手段。
如果设计师开始使用一种设计工具，而不是使用笔和纸，那么他或她的移动速度就不够快，浪费了从不可避免的错误中学习的时间。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;6他们不使用最新的设计工具they-dont-use-the-latest-design-tools&quot;&gt;6.他们不使用最新的设计工具/They don’t use the latest design tools&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;我知道这似乎很琐碎。&lt;/strong&gt;但是现实是，自满会杀死人。如果产品设计师不了解该行业使用的最新工具，则可能表明他/她没有积极寻求提高效率的方法。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;7他们责怪开发they-blame-developers&quot;&gt;7.他们责怪开发/They blame developers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;如果设计的最终实现与预期不符（请阅读：pixel-perfect），那是设计者的错。他或她或者不了解什么在技术上可行，或者在编写代码时没有与开发人员有效地沟通以进行课程纠正。应该期望设计师创造愉悦的体验，其中包括与队友互动的经历。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/01/7-signs-of-an-underachieving-product-designer/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020/03/01/7-signs-of-an-underachieving-product-designer/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
